planyourwedding.my 2016-05-17

# PlanYourWedding: Your wedding ideas and inspiration!

Tornado Internet Sdn. Bhd. is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) we collect from users of our website, located at www.planyourwedding.my, ("Website") and Services (as defined in the Terms of Use). Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given in our Terms of Use located at planyourwedding.my. 

By using and visiting the Site, you agree to this Policy and the uses made of personal information as set forth herein or amended hereafter.

#### What this Privacy Policy Covers

> This Privacy Policy covers the Planyourwedding.my's treatment of personally identifiable information that Planyourwedding.my collects when you are on this Website and when you use the Planyourwedding.my's services. This policy does not describe information collection policies on other sites, including those linked to or from the Site.

#### Type of Information Collected and How It's used

> The Site does not collect any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") about you other than information that you affirmatively choose to submit to us and pertaining to yourself as well as information which may be obtained from your browser during registration.
> 
> Such identifiable information may be your Name, Contact Number, Address, E-mail address, Company Address, Company Name and Company Telephone Number.
> 
> Once you register with us and sign in to our services, you are anonymous to us.
> 
> We will not, however, share any such Personal Information with other entities except for such entities that have been authorised to carry out specific services for the Planyourwedding.my.
> 
> We may also contact you from time to time to obtain your latest Personal Information for the purposes of serving you more efficiently and effectively.
> 
> Unless you object, the Personal Information may be additionally used to:
> 
>   * send e-mail base newsletters and other information to you as you request and to notify you from time to time about services offered by the Planyourwedding.my or other entities associated with Planyourwedding.my,
>   * monitor persons using and accessing the Website,
>   * profile and/or analyse the persons using and accessing the Website and their pattern and manner of usage,
>   * to customise the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products,
> 
whether directly or through our partners or affiliates but for the sole purpose of fulfilling the functions above.
> 
> You are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your Personal Information used for purposes not directly related to the Website at the point where we ask for it.
> 
> If you do not wish to have information on you used in any of the aforesaid manner, you can e-mail us through enquiries@planyourweddin.my.
> 
> If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, you can click on the unsubscribe link in our emails to remove your email address from our mailing list.
> 
> Except as provided herein and as required by law, your Personal Information will not be made available to third parties without your consent.
> 
> Planyourwedding.my may use your Personal Information for any purpose which Planyourwedding.my may deem fit in its sole discretion.
> 
> If you request that Planyourwedding.my does not use your Personal Information in any particular manner, we will adopt all reasonable measures to observe your request but we may still use or disclose that Personal Information if s Planyourwedding.my believes that the use and disclosure is reasonably necessary under the governing laws.
> 
> Planyourwedding.my shall preserve the contents of any communications which you send if Planyourwedding.my is of the view that there is a legal requirement for doing so. Your communications may be monitored for purposes of trouble-shooting or maintenance purposes. 

#### Cookies

> A cookie is used to monitor the use of the Website and to gather information such as the sections of the website visited and other website usage information.
> 
> The information is aggregated prior to such use and does not include any Personal Information. The Site uses cookies to serve you more efficiently when you revisit the Site.
> 
> Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, you can set your browser to refuse all cookies or notify you when you receive a cookie and you will have the opportunity to either accept or reject it in each instance.
> 
> Please note, however, that some parts of the services offered by the Planyourwedding.my on this Site may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

#### Security

> Planyourwedding.my uses its best endeavours to store all Personal Information on servers with restricted access, and all electronic storage and transmission of Personal Information are secured with appropriate security technologies. Not to withstand the foregoing, Planyourwedding.my cannot guarantee that such precautions would render the Site and Planyourwedding.my's servers immune to security breaches.

#### Hyperlinks

> When you are on the Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond the control of Planyourwedding.my including hyperlinks to advertisers, merchants, sponsors, and content partners. 
> 
> You acknowledge that when you click on a hyperlink that leaves the Site, the site you are directed to is not within Planyourwedding.my's control, and you acknowledge that Planyourwedding.my shall not be responsible for those sites or any damages or losses incurred by you resulting thereto. 

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

> Planyourwedding.my may change and update this Privacy Policy, including materially changing the use made of personal information described herein. Any change or update to our privacy policy will be posted on our Web site under "Privacy Policy" at least 30 days prior to their implementation. Your continued use of the Web site after the effective date of any changes will constitute your acceptance of all of the changes.

#### Effective date

> This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 2013.

#### Contact Information

> If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please fill up the Feedback form from the Site or send an email to enquiries@planyourwedding.my.
> 
> We welcome your feedback. Should you feel dissatisfied with any of our services, please contact us at Tel: +603.8051.5528
